wintrillions.com 2014-12-05

# Wintrillions.com Privacy policy

Thank you for visiting [Wintrillions.com](http://www.wintrillions.com/). We are totally committed to protecting your security and ensuring your right to privacy. The following is a disclosure of our privacy policy and explains how Wintrillions.com uses, and if necessary, discloses your personal information. It is important that you know and fully understand the WinTrillions Privacy Policy before using our website.

### Collection of information

As part of the WinTrillions subscription process we ask for your name, address and other contact information. We also ask for billing information, some preferences and some other information. While some of the information you provide is essential to run our business, other information is optional, clearly marked as such, and may be given at your discretion. The information you provide allows us to provide an efficient service to you and helps us improve our level of service to better meet your needs.

### How we use the information

The information that you provide to Wintrillions is used to fulfil your requests for our products and services and to respond to any inquiries about our offerings. We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won lotteries or contests, when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfil some of your requests, or to contact you about your account with us. We also may use non-personally identifiable information that we collect in order to improve the design and content of our websites and to collect usage statistics.

We may use your contact information to send you updates, promotions, newsletters or news regarding our Website or our products and services.

Additionally, Wintrillions.com may disclose personal information when required by law and in response to a legal process such as in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. Otherwise, Wintrillions will never intentionally share your personal information with a 3rd party without your permission.

We will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for any purposes.

If you want to opt out from our communications you can do it whenever you want by sending an email to support@wintrillions.com requesting so. 

### Cookies

To enhance your experience while visiting Wintrillions, many of our web pages use Cookies. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on yourcomputer that identifies you as a unique user. This piece of data contains information to link your computer to your WinTrillions account. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personal information you may have provided; they simply make your time on the site simpler and more enjoyable.

### Security

WinTrillions takes every precaution to protect user information against loss, misuse and alteration. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we pledge to do our utmost to prevent against any such occurrences. We have in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access to the information we maintain in our systems.

Wintrillions.com is owned and operated by:   
Ledonford Ltd.   
3 Athinodorou Street, 2025 Dasoupoli, Strovolos, Nicosia, Cyprus.   
Tel: 44 203 139 9052
